seriously almost let it stop me I don't
have a pen
I can't write down the idea it's not 30
or even know that I once bought 30 so I
mean sorry that I was on slot 30 now
it's about 31 so the 31st Apple one of
the ideas I had during the social
venture talks was inspired by Tanya who
has a company called Junko it is a slow
fashion comfy and although I'm not a big
fashion person I definitely loved her
artwork on clothing and part of the
business model is pop-ups and finding
pop-up spaces and I'm sure there's a way
to create an app to enable that for
people to be able to come together with
other artisans so other slow fashion
arsons
create figure out what pop-ups are
available and coordinate with people a
time and space that works for you
there's people around there's very
distracting keynote nature and so that
is idea number 31 is a I guess pop-up
space directory slash slow fashion
market health was it kind of to the
other idea was it like an Etsy for slope
fashion just that so you can get people
to locally make you small batch clothes
that fit you for your body type and
working with local designers and making
it accessible to people
yeah that is Apple number 31